soccerpulse.com 2008-06-16

# None

This document was last updated March 16th, 2008.  

Soccerpulse.com is committed to protecting your privacy. The following privacy statement describes our practice with respect to the collection and use of your personally identifiable information (personal information) on this Web site. By using this Web site, you consent to the terms of our privacy statement and to Soccerpulse.com's processing of personal information for the purposes stated below.

Soccerpulse.com may require you to provide us with personal information if you would like to participate in some activities available on, or benefit from services offered on, this Web site. We endeavor to limit our requests for personal information to information we believe is minimally necessary to achieve our stated collection purposes. Personal information collected on this Web site is often limited to e-mail address, country or location but may include additional information when needed to provide a service you requested. For example, if you choose a service or transaction that requires payment, such as making a donation on the Soccerpulse.com donation page, we will request personal information necessary for billing and/or shipping such as name, address, telephone number and credit card number.

Also, in order to improve our services and the quality of the Web site, Soccerpulse.com offers you the opportunity to provide your suggestions and contributions by completing a Contact Us form which collects personal information such as name and e-mail address. Please note that any comments or materials sent to us, including feedback data, such as questions, comments, suggestions and any other responses are deemed to be non-confidential. We have no obligation with respect to such responses, Soccerpulse.com shall be free to use, reproduce, distribute and publicly display such comments and materials without reference to you personally. Soccerpulse.com is also free to use any ideas, concepts, know-how or techniques contained in such responses for any purpose whatsoever.

Soccerpulse.com uses your personal information collected on this Web site primarily for the following purposes:

  * To deliver services, such as newsletters
  * To ensure our Web site is relevant to your needs.
  * To help us create and publish content most relevant to you.
  * To allow you access to limited-entry areas of our Web site as appropriate.
  * To contact you in response to sign up forms such as Contact Us or The Discussion Board.

to provide us with your personal information on this Web site, we may transfer that information to Soccerpulse.com’s affiliates and subsidiaries or to Soccerpulse.com’s third party service providers, across borders, and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world and by using this Web site, you consent to any such transfer of personal information outside of your country or jurisdiction.

Soccerpulse.com occasionally hires third parties to provide certain services available on our Web site or made available on our behalf. We will only provide those third party providers the personal information they need to deliver their services, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.

Soccerpulse.com may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the requirements of law or comply with legal process served on this Web site, protect and defend the rights or property of Soccerpulse.com and its family of Web sites or act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of Soccerpulse.com employees, users of Soccerpulse.com products or services, or members of the public.

Soccerpulse.com reserves the right to transfer personal information to third parties as part of any corporate reorganization process including, but not limited, mergers, acquisitions, and sales of all or substantially all of our assets.

Soccerpulse.com does not otherwise use, sell, rent, share or otherwise disclose your personal information to any third parties.

Soccerpulse.com uses non-personal information such as demographic data to analyze and develop marketing strategy and to determine how you found about us, your interests regarding our products and services and how to further improve this Web site based upon user data. We may share such non-personal data with third parties.

Soccerpulse.com provides you the opportunity to exercise an opt-out choice if you do not want to receive emails from us or updates regarding new services offered on this Web site or if you do not want us to share your personal information with third parties. The opt-out choice may be exercised at the points where personal information is collected by un-ticking the appropriate box. If you do not have exercised the opt-out option at the point where personal information is collected you may also do it by contacting us at [webmaster@soccerpulse.com](mailto:webmaster@soccerpulse.com). We will process your unsubscribe as soon as possible, but please be aware that in some circumstances you may receive a few more messages until the unsubscribe is processed.

Soccerpulse.com uses "cookies" and other tracking technologies. A "cookie" is a small text file that may be used to collect information about Web site activity. For example, when someone visits the Web site, a cookie is placed on the user's machine (if the user accepts cookies) or is read if the user has visited the Web site previously. You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser, but please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, you will need to re-enter your original user ID and password to gain access to certain parts of the Web site.

Soccerpulse.com uses an email delivery and marketing third party provider to send emails that you have agreed to receive. Pixel tags and cookies are used in those email messages and at this Web site to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising and how visitors use our Web site. For more information about the technology used to deliver our emails, or to set your browser to reject cookies, please click here.

If you have agreed to receive emails from us, those emails may contain advertising about goods and services that we think might be of interest to you. In order to understand how our readers interact with the emails and the content that we send, we use pixels in the text in order to understand who has opened the emails that they have been sent. In order to provide our content in the most interesting way, we also use pixels to learn whether you can receive emails in text or html form. If you click on a link in the email, we may set a cookie on your browser. If you visit this Web site as a result of clicking on a link, we are able to understand how you interact with the pages of our Web site through the combination of the cookie and pixels set on the pages of our Web site. This enables us to understand what interested you in our emails and what did not, and what interests you about our Web site and what does not. We can then try to send you more interesting information in the future. Please note that this information is for our use only - we do not disclose or share this information with any third parties.

Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies allows us to improve our Web site and your Web experience. We may also analyze information that does not contain personal information for trends and statistics.

This statement applies solely to information collected on this Web site. This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we have no control or influence over the privacy practices of such other Web sites. We encourage you to read such other Web sites' privacy statement in order to understand whether and how they process data about your visit to their site.

Soccerpulse.com provides you with an opportunity to access your personal information to ensure it is correct, accurate and current. To edit your personal information, please go to the forum and follow the instructions listed in the “My Profile”. Some services offered on this Web site may collect information that is not accessible via the Preferences Center. In such cases, you can access your personal information by contacting Soccerpulse.com as described at the bottom of this statement. We will make reasonable efforts to incorporate the changes as soon as practicable.

With effect for the future, Soccerpulse.com reserves the right to change this privacy statement from time to time. When we do, we will also revise the "last update" date at the top of this privacy statement. For material changes to this privacy statement, we will notify you be placing a notice on this Web site.

Soccerpulse.com endeavors to take reasonable and appropriate steps to protect your personal information from unauthorized access or disclosure. However, we do not warrant or represent that your personal information is completely safe from hackers and other security threats. If you have any questions about the security on this site, you can send an email to [webmaster@soccerpulse.com](mailto:webmaster@soccerpulse.com).

If you have comments or questions with respect to this statement, please contact us at [webmaster@soccerpulse.com](mailto:webmaster@soccerpulse.com) or by mail to:

Soccerpulse.com  
Attn: C. Meisner  
410 - 7 Vimy Ave  
Halifax, Nova Scotia  
Canada  
B3M 4P9
